原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
他们都恨你  曼达人
They all hate you, Mando.
因为你是传奇
Because you're a legend!
翻译     哈里星球    累
他们之中有多少人有追踪器
How many of them had fobs?
他们都有
All of them.
你知道他们会怎么做吗
Any idea what they gonna happen to it?
我没问  这违反工会规定
I didn't ask. It's against the Guild Code.
校对     累
《曼达洛人》前情提要
时间轴     累
索尔根
Sorgan.
没有星际港  没有工业中心
No star port, no industrial centers,
后期     累
人烟稀少
no population density.
我要把他留在这里
I'm leaving him here.
和我一起走  那孩子就过不上好日子了
Traveling with me, that's no life for a kid.
总监     星星与野狗
他们知道孩子在这里
They know he's here.
嗯
Yes.
他们不会罢休的
Then they'll keep coming.
对
Yes.
星球大战
把孩子交出来  曼达人
Hand over the child, Mando.
我可能会留你条命
I might let you live.
抓稳了
Hold on.
挺住
Come on.
我把你带回去就行  不论生死
I can bring you in warm or I can bring you in cold.
那是我的台词
That's my line.
曼达洛人
第一季  第五集
持枪歹徒
燃料泄露
Losing fuel.
这里是莫斯艾斯利星际塔台
This is Mos Eisley Tower.
我们正在跟踪你
We are tracking you.
驶向35号泊位  完毕
Head for bay three-five, over.
收到
Copy that.
锁定35泊位
Locked in for three-five.
你毁了我一个机器人  你得付出代价
You damage one of my droids, you'll pay for it.
让它们不要靠近我的飞船
Just keep them away from my ship.
是吗  你觉得这是个好主意吗
Yeah? You think that's a good idea, do ya?
我们来看看你的飞船
Let's look at your ship.
你看看
Look at that.
上面有很多积碳呢
Ugh, you got a lot of carbon scorin' building up top.
对
Yeah.
乍一看我以为你跟别人交火过呢
If I didn't know better, I'd think you were in a shootout.
那个要特殊工具
Special tool for that one.
我得把这个转一下
I am gonna have to rotate that.
燃料泄漏了
You got a fuel leak.
瞧瞧  这也太惨了
Look at that, this is a mess.
你居然还能降落  你可得破费了
How did you even land? That's gonna set you back.
我有500帝国币
I've got 500 Imperial Credits.
就这么多吗  你们觉得呢
That's all you got? Well, what do you guys think?
起码够付机库的钱了
That should at least cover the hangar.
我会想办法筹钱的
I'll get you your money.
这话我听过
I've heard that before.
-记住...  -知道
- Just remember... - Yeah.
不要机器人  我听见了  不用说第二遍
No droids. I heard ya. You don't have to say it twice.
天啊
Jeez.
王鼠
Womp rat.
我跟
I'm in.
再加码三根螺栓和一个激发器
And I am gonna raise you three bolts and a motivator.
快  把我的爆能步枪拿来
Quick, grab my blaster rifle.
你最好待在飞船里
I'd stay in that ship if I were you.
什么
What?
乖  乖
Now, now.
让派丽好好看看你
Let Peli take a good look at you.
很好  这就对了
All right, there you go.
那个赏金猎人
Did that bounty hunter
把你一个人丢在又大又破的飞船上了吗
leave you all alone in that big nasty ship?
我怎么知道这是啥  别催
How do I know what it is? Give me a second.
你想吃东西吗
All right. Now, would you like some food?
你饿吗
Are you hungry?
给我们拿点吃的  快
Okay. Fetch us something to eat. Quick!
我也不知道...  带骨头的东西吧
I don't know... Something with bones in it.
好
Okay.
这样吧
Now, here's the plan.
我会在曼达洛人回来之前照看你
I am going to look after you until The Mandalorian gets back,
然后我要加收照看你的钱
and then I'm gonna charge him extra for watching you.
明白了吧  亮眼睛
You see how that works? Yeah, bright eyes?
咱俩是一伙的
We're a team.
机器人
Hey, droid,
我是赏金猎人  想找活干
I'm a hunter. I'm lookin' for some work
很遗憾  塔图因的赏金猎人工会关闭了
Unfortunately, the Bounty Guild no longer operates from Tatooine.
我不是找工会的活
I'm not looking for Guild work.
即便这样  情况也差不多
I am afraid that does not improve your situation,
至少我的计算是这样
at least by my calculation.
再想想  金属壳
Think again, tin can.
如果你想找活就过来坐吧  朋友
If you're looking for work, have a seat, my friend.
我叫托洛  托洛·卡利肯
Name's Toro, Toro Calican.
来吧  别紧张
Come on, relax.
我离开中环时拿了这个赏金定位碟
Picked up this Bounty Puck before I left the Mid Rim.
芬尼克·尚德  一个杀手
Fennec Shand, an Assassin.
听说新共和国把她的雇主们
Heard she's been on the run
关起来以后  她就一直在逃亡
ever since the New Republic put all her employers in lockdown.
我知道名字
I know the name.
我追着这个跟踪器来到这里
I followed this tracking fob here.
位置数据显示她跨越了沙丘海
Now the positional data suggests she's headed out beyond the Dune Sea.
这任务应该挺简单的
Should be an easy job.
祝你好运
Well, good luck with that.
等等  等等  你不是在找活吗
Wait, wait, wait, hey. I thought you needed work?
你在工会待多久了
How long you've been with the Guild?
够久了
Long enough.
显然不够  芬尼克·尚德是一个精英雇佣兵
Clearly not. Fennec Shand is an elite mercenary.
她专为顶级犯罪集团杀人
She made her name killing for all the top crime syndicates,
包括赫特人
including the Hutts.
你要去找她  肯定活不过明天
If you go after her, you won't make it past sunrise.
这是我的第一个任务
This is my first job.
所有的钱都归你
You can keep the money, all of it.
我需要这个任务进入工会
I just need this job to get into the Guild.
我一个人干不了
I can't do it alone.
半小时后在35机库等我
Meet me at Hangar three-five in half an hour.
带上两辆飞行摩托  把追踪器给我
Bring two speeder bikes and give me the tracking fob.
别担心  都记下来了
Don't worry, got it all memorized.
半小时
Half an hour.
看来你得跟我混了  搭档
Looks like you're stuck with me now, partner.
我醒了  我醒了
I'm awake! I'm awake!
-他在哪里  -安静
- Where is he? - Quiet!
没事了  你把它吵醒了
It's okay. You woke it up.
你知道我花了多久才把它哄睡着吗
Do you have any idea how long it took me to get it to sleep?
给我
Give him to me.
别急
Not so fast!
你不能就这样把孩子一个人留下
You can't just leave a child all alone like that.
你有很多东西要学  比如带孩子
You know, you have an awful lot to learn about raisin' a young one.
总之我已经开始修理漏油的地方
Anyway, I started the repair on the fuel leak.
好了  我有些价钱问题想和你谈谈
There you go. I had a couple setbacks I want to talk to you about.
我按你的要求  没有使用机器人
You know, I didn't use any droids, as requested,
所以花的时间比我的预期要长很多
so it took me a lot longer than I expected.
但我觉得你应该付得起钱
But I figured you were good for the money
毕竟你还有一个孩子要养
since you have an extra mouth to feed.
谢谢
Thank you.
看来我猜对了  你找到工作了  是吗
Oh, I guess I was right. You got a job, didn't you?
光是给这些机器人充电
You know, it's costing me a lot of money
就花了我很多钱
to keep these droids even powered up.
曼达人  怎么样  还不错吧
Hey, Mando, what do you think? Not too shabby, huh?
想啥呢  这里又不是科雷利亚  夫人
What'd you expect? This ain't Corellia. Ma'am.
-怎么了  -看前面
- What's going on? - Look. Up ahead.
塔斯肯袭击者
Tusken Raiders.
我听本地人谈论了这个肮脏的东西
I heard the locals talking about this filth.
塔斯肯人认为他们才是本地人
Tuskens think they're the locals.
其他人都是非法闯入
Everyone else is just trespassing.
不管他们怎么称呼自己  最好离我们远点
Whatever they call themselves, they best keep their distance.
是吗  那你自己说吧
Yeah? Why don't you tell them yourself?
放松
Relax.
-你干嘛  -谈判
- What are you doing? - Negotiating.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我们要通过他们的土地
We need passage across their land.
-把双筒望远镜给我  -为什么
- Let me see the binocs. - Why?
什么
What?
-那可是全新的  -是吗  现在不是了
- Those were brand new. - Yeah? They were.
隐蔽
Get down.
什么
What?
告诉我  你看到了什么
All right, tell me what you see.
沙地兽
Dewback.
骑手还在上面
Looks like the rider is still attached.
是她吗  那是目标吗
Is that her? Is that the target?
我不知道
I don't know.
我过去  你掩护我
I'll go. You cover me.
保持隐蔽
Stay down.
是她吗  她死了吗
Well, is it her? Is she dead?
也是一个赏金猎人
It's another bounty hunter.
别全贪了啊
Hey, I hope you don't plan on keeping all that stuff for yourself.
好歹给我留个爆能枪
Can I at least have that blaster?
趴下
Get down!
曼达人
Mando!
怎么回事
What happened?
狙击螺栓
Sniper bolt.
只有MK改装步枪才能打出来
Only an MK-modified rifle could make that shot.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
嗯  打中我的贝斯卡钢甲了
Yeah. Hit me in the beskar,
这个距离  贝斯卡钢甲能抗住
and at that range beskar held up.
等等  我没穿贝斯卡钢甲
Wait, I don't wear any beskar.
的确
Nope.
那我们该怎么办
Well, so what do we do?
你看到那枪是从哪里打来的吗
You see where that shot came from?
嗯  从山脊那打过来的
Yeah, it came from that ridge.
好  我们等到天黑
Okay, we're gonna wait until dark.
如果她跑了呢
Well, what if she escapes?
现在是她占领高地
She's got the high ground.
她会等我们采取行动的
She'll wait for us to make the first move.
我休息一会  你先守着  注意隐蔽
I'm gonna rest. You take the first watch. Stay low!
太阳下山了  该走了  曼达人
All right, suns are down. Time to ride, Mando.
快点  醒醒
Come on, wake up.
看看你  在工作中睡着了  老头子
Look at you, asleep on the job, old man.
说完了吗
You done?
嗯  我就是来叫你的  走吧
Yeah. I was just, you know, waking you up. Come on.
骑上摩托
Get on your bike.
尽快开向那些岩石
Ride as fast as you can towards those rocks.
这就是你的计划  她会把我们从摩托上狙下来的
That's your plan? She'll snipe us right off the bikes.
这是闪击电荷
It's a flash charge.
我们交替射击  就可以短暂致盲所有角度
We alternate shots, it'll blind any scope temporarily.
再加上我们的速度  就有机会了
Combine that with our speed and we got a chance.
机会
A chance?
这次行动是你的主意  准备好
Hey, you wanted this. Get ready.
开始
Now!
别急  芬尼克
Not so fast, Fennec.
注意力分散得不错
Nice distraction.
是啊  干得漂亮  搭档
Yeah, good work, partner.
自己铐上
Cuff yourself.
去找你的爆能枪吧
Why don't you go find your blaster?
曼达洛人
A Mandalorian.
我很久没见过你这种人了
It's been a long time since I've seen one of your kind.
去过尼瓦罗吗
Ever been to Nevarro?
我听说那里的状况不太好
I hear things didn't go so well there,
但是看起来你轻易就脱身了
but it looks like you got off easy.
我们把你上交后  你就不用想着去尼瓦罗
You don't have to worry about gettin' to Nevarro,
或者其他地方了
or anywhere else, once we turn you in.
我真的应该谢谢你
You know, I really should thank you.
你是我进入工会的入场券
You're my ticket into the Guild.
不客气
You're welcome.
看来有个人要步行了
Looks like one of us has to walk.
我们也可以拖着你
Or we could drag you.
你有什么打算
All right, so what is the plan?
你去找我们看到的沙地兽
I need you to go find that dewback we saw.
然后把你和我的赏金还有摩托留在这里吗
And leave you here with my bounty and my ride?
你想多了  曼达人
Yeah, I don't think so, Mando.
好吧  我去
Okay, I'll do it.
看着她  别让她靠近摩托
Watch her, and don't let her get near the bike.
她死了对我们没好处
She's no good to us dead.
好久没睡这么好了
Oh, it's been a while.
瞧  太阳快出来了
Oh, look, the suns are coming up.
安静
Quiet.
我还有时间赶去莫斯埃斯帕
Look, there's still time to make my rendezvous in Mos Espa.
载我过去  我可以付你双倍的价钱
Take me to it and I can pay you double the price on my head.
我不在乎钱
I don't care about the money.
所以曼达洛人笑纳所有的钱了
Oh, so the Mandalorian keeps all the money for himself.
那是我放他一马
Only because I let him.
感觉不是呢
Doesn't seem that way.
我感觉都是他说了算
I mean, it seems like he's calling all the shots.
你知道啥
Shows what you know.
曼达人是我雇的  这是我的任务
I hired Mando, this is my job.
把你交上去  我就能正式加入赏金猎人工会
Bringin' you in will make me a full member of the Bounty Hunters Guild.
你已经拥有工会更看重的东西了
You already have something the Guild values far more than me.
你只是没发现而已
You just don't see it.
-什么  -曼达洛人
- What? - The Mandalorian.
光是他的盔甲就比我的赏金值钱
His armor alone's worth more than my bounty.
我说了  我不在乎钱
I already told you, I don't care about the money.
那你应该在乎名声吧
Then think what it would do for your reputation.
一个曼达洛人在尼瓦罗向工会开枪
A Mandalorian shot up the Guild on Nevarro,
抢走重要目标以后逃跑了
took some high value target and went rogue.
那个曼达洛人
That Mandalorian?
我说了  曼达洛人可不常见
Like I said, you don't see many.
你把那个叛徒上交工会
You bring the Guild that traitor,
他们肯定会热烈欢迎你加入的
and they'll welcome you with open arms.
你的名字将会成为传奇
Your name will be legendary.
我们怎么能确定是他
How can we be sure he's the one?
据说目标还在他身边
Word is, he still has the target with him.
而且是个孩子
Some say it's a child.
如果你害怕和他战斗  不用担心
Look, if you're afraid to take him on, fear not.
我可以帮你
I can help you with that.
听取我的建议  孩子
Take some advice, kid.
你想成为赏金猎人吗
You wanna be a bounty hunter?
做对自己最有利的买卖  然后活下来
Make the best deal for yourself and survive.
这是个好建议
That's good advice,
但是如果我帮你解锁  我就死定了
but if I took those binders off of you I'd be a dead man.
既然曼达洛人比你值钱  那
And if the Mandalorian's worth more than you are, well...
谁不想成为传奇呢
Who wouldn't want to be a legend?
谢谢你的提醒
Thanks for the tip.
这么久啊  曼达人
Took you long enough, Mando.
看来现在我说了算啊  搭档
Looks like I'm calling the shots now. Huh, partner?
放下爆能枪  把手举起来
Drop your blaster and raise 'em.
把他铐起来
Cuff him.
你是工会的叛徒  曼达人
You're a Guild traitor, Mando.
我敢打赌
And I'm willing to bet that
这就是你协助逃跑的目标
this here is the target you helped escape.
你没有看上去那么笨
You're smarter than you look.
芬尼克说得对
Fennec was right.
把你上交不但会让我成为工会的一员
Bringing you in won't just make me a member of the Guild,
还会让我成为传奇
it'll make me legendary.
-退后  -一定要救它
- Stay back. - Gotta get it.
哪去了
Where is it?
你在这里呀
There you are.
你在躲我们吗
Are you hiding from us?
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
没关系  我知道
That's all right. I know.
你耳朵这么大  一定很吵吧
That was really loud for your big old ears, wasn't it?
没事了
It's okay.
好好照顾他
Be careful with him.
你没拿到报酬吧
So, I take it you didn't get paid?
够了吗
That cover me?
嗯嗯  够了
Yeah. Yes, this is gonna cover you.
维修机器人  把这个拖出去
All right, Pit Droids! Let's drag this outta here!
我不知道  拖到拜加峡谷吧
I don't know, drag it to Beggar's Canyon.